jump in you're trained to realize that I
跳进来，你受过训练，意识到我
forgot my laptop but now I had my laptop
忘记了我的笔记本电脑，但是现在我有了我的笔记本电脑
with me but for 30 seconds I was like oh
和我在一起但是30秒钟我就像在哦
my on my lap yeah don't ask it was
在我的大腿上拉屎我是的，不要问那是
very early so I flew via Paris my plane
很早，所以我乘飞机飞过巴黎
was delayed and I know we all most got a
被耽搁了，我知道我们大多数人都有
crash with harbor while coming here I
我来这里时与港口相撞
just arrived well not even one hour ago
一小时前才到达
so everything is good so I'm I have some
所以一切都很好，我有一些
as well I have a bunch of demos so
我也有很多演示
naturally it will goes so my name is
自然会走，所以我的名字是
David Alaba say I work at Oracle and
David Alaba说我在Oracle工作，
today we're going to discuss a project
今天我们要讨论一个项目
harridan before we do so as I mentioned
我之前提到过的哈里丹
even though I have a French accent I'm
即使我有法国口音
coming from Belgium where I work for
来自我工作的比利时
Oracle I'm reporting to the US and this
Oracle我正在向美国报告
is someone so this is me in Sweden in
是某人，所以这是我在瑞典
2017 so as a focus and someone in the
2017年为重点，
audience tweeted that it's not a real
观众发推文说这不是真的
conference unless you read the Oracle
会议，除非您阅读了Oracle
syllabus that meant statement at least
至少要声明的教学大纲
once so please enjoy another disclaimer
一次，因此请享受另一个免责声明
is this one I don't know if anybody of
我不知道这是谁吗
you are using those new Mac keyboard the
您正在使用那些新的Mac键盘
butterfly keyboard I will do demos and
蝴蝶键盘，我会做演示，
I'm pretty sure that I will some of my
我很确定我会
demo will not work it's really because
演示无法正常工作，这是因为
of the keyboard and I will show you that
键盘，我会告诉你
so the agenda for today we're going to
所以今天的议程我们要
discuss halide on so I will start with
讨论卤化物，所以我将从
an introduction on illidan so what it is
关于伊利丹的介绍，这是什么
and then I will basically show you a
然后我基本上会告诉你
little in action and hopefully we will
行动不多，希望我们会
have some time at the end for answering
最后有一些时间来回答
questions so Haledon first anybody has a
问题，所以Haledon首先有人
guess what Haledon I mean the term
猜猜Haledon是什么意思
celadon means no well with normal I
青瓷意味着我正常
didn't know either so we had to check on
也不知道，所以我们不得不检查
Wikipedia so written is a type of bird
这样写的维基百科是一种鸟
with a slender streamlined body and long
细长的流线型身体和长
pointed wings which hello great
尖的翅膀你好
maneuverability and very efficient
机动性和非常高效
flight it's basically a bird no but
基本上是只鸟
that's the marketing way of and the good
这就是行销的方式和好处
thing about that type of that type of
关于那种类型的事情
bird is that they are typically very
鸟是他们通常非常
agile when it comes to cloud
涉及云的敏捷
and hence the names so hidden accident
因此名字如此隐蔽
dot IO what it is well simply put in
点IO只需简单地输入
Haledon is basically a set of Java
Haledon基本上是Java的集合
libraries for developing micro services
开发微服务的库
it's project a project that we have
这是一个我们拥有的项目
launched October last year so it's
去年10月推出，所以
pretty new it's open source obviously
很新，显然是开源的
it's Apache V - everything is on github
它是Apache V-一切都在github上
so github.com slash oracle slash Haledon
所以github.com斜线oracle斜线Haledon
we're on twitter we also have a public
我们在推特上我们也有一个公众
slack channel and we have this
松弛的渠道，我们有这个
helenandheid high website so if you just
helenandheid高级网站，如果您只是
have to remember one resource is one
必须记住一种资源就是一种
link just go to an Haledon that I owe
链接只是转到我欠的Haledon
everything is linked from there and you
一切都从那里链接到你
will see that it's a very well-designed
会看到这是一个精心设计的
website even though it has been designed
网站，即使它已经设计
by Oracle so before we start
因此，在开始之前
where does Haledon fit so this is
Haledon适合哪里，所以这是
basically our view of the Java micro
基本上我们对Java micro的看法
services framework landscape it's our
服务框架景观，这是我们的
view so don't take this as kind of
查看，所以不要以这种方式
Universal view of the market but it's
市场的普遍看法，但这是
basically I would categorize the market
基本上我会把市场分类
so we basically see three type of
所以我们基本上看到三种类型的
frameworks to write micro services with
编写微服务的框架
Java first we have the full stack
Java首先，我们有完整的堆栈
framework such as bring good for example
例如带来良好的框架
Java EE Jakarta II would also fit there
Java EE Jakarta II也将适用于此
then we have all the frameworks which
那么我们有所有的框架
are based on the micro profile
基于微观特征
specification they are clearly more
规格他们显然更多
lightweight than full stack frame works
比全栈框架轻巧
in terms of capability maybe they don't
在能力方面，也许他们没有
have all the capability and all the
有所有的能力和所有的
bellows and all the bells and whistles
波纹管和所有的钟声和口哨声
that we have on full stack framework but
我们拥有完整的堆栈框架，但是
there are more agile more nimble than
敏捷比敏捷更强大
full stack frameworks and then at the
全栈框架，然后在
bottom we have Mike what we call micro
底部有麦克，我们称之为微
frameworks typically very lean very
框架通常非常精益
lightweight frameworks
轻量级框架
again with less capability than the
再次具有比
micro profile based one but those
微型配置文件，但那些
framework are also very attractive so in
框架也很有吸引力
terms of micro profile based frameworks
基于微概要文件的框架的术语
we have openly BRT payara quark use
我们已经公开使用BRT payara夸克
those days I believe that dontel is now
那些日子我相信dontel现在
under flight on the micro framework side
在微型框架方面正在飞行
we are frameworks such as javelin spark
我们是标枪之类的框架
micro node and so on so where does Helen
微节点等等海伦在哪里
on fit and I think that Helen is quite
身体健康，我认为海伦很
unique in the sense that it fits at two
恰好适合两个
level it fit at the micro profile level
使其适合微观轮廓水平
so written with a lid on you can
所以写上有盖就可以
using all the micro profiles API but it
使用所有微型配置文件API，但它
also sit at the micro frameworks level
也坐在微观框架层面
because you will see that valid on you
因为你会看到对你有效
basically have choice we have two
基本上有选择，我们有两个
programming models and it's up to you
编程模型，由您决定
the developer to decide which approach
开发人员决定采用哪种方法
you want to use so we have added NAC
您要使用，所以我们添加了NAC
which is really a pure Java SE way of
这实际上是纯Java SE的方式
writing micro services so that's why we
编写微服务，这就是为什么我们
call that a micro framework it's
称之为微框架
basically a functional Styles we are
基本上是我们的功能样式
having some reactive Coverity and it's
有一些反应性Coverity，
very transparent so there is no hidden
非常透明，所以没有隐藏
magic like injection for example in a
像注射一样的魔术
Libyan al-anon you see you basically
利比亚Al-anon您基本上看到了您
write what you want to expect and we
写出您想要的东西，我们
will see some code later on and then
稍后会看到一些代码，然后
based on that we have written an MP
基于此，我们编写了一个MP
which basically comply to the macro
基本上符合宏
profile specification it's a more
配置文件规范
declarative style than a lead on AC it's
声明式的风格比AC的领先优势
really imperative imperative driven so
真正当务之急是当务之急
in a lead on MP you will obviously use
在MP的领先优势中，您显然会使用
for example annotation something that
例如注释一些
you will not do on the AC side in terms
就交流而言，您不会这样做
of API we're really talking about micro
API方面，我们实际上是在谈论微
profiles so we are using CGI Jack's
配置文件，所以我们使用的是CGI Jack's
arrest Jason PJs and B and so on and so
逮捕Jason PJ和B等，依此类推
on so if you are coming from the micro
因此，如果您来自微型
profile or the Java space that's
概要文件或Java空间
typically where you will go you will I
通常你会去哪里，我会
like to use the Holy Name MP programming
喜欢使用圣名MP编程
model now if we look at the architecture
现在来看一下架构
of harridan AC we have three core
哈里丹AC我们有三个核心
components we have a web server
我们有一个Web服务器的组件
component we have a configuration
组件我们有一个配置
component and we have a security
组件，我们有一个安全
security component so as I mentioned
正如我提到的安全组件
there's no hidden magic with the Halidon
Halidon没有隐藏的魔术
AC so it's simple transparent no
AC，所以很简单透明
injection no inversion of control no
注射否控制反转否
packaging tricks and so on and so on at
包装技巧等等，等等
the end of the day what we are
一天结束时我们是什么
generating is a pure java c application
生成是一个纯Java C应用程序
under the hood the web server component
Web服务器组件的内部
is using nettie so that's something that
正在使用nettie，这就是
makes a lot of sense then based on that
在此基础上讲很有意义
we have a Halligan MP so basically we
我们有一个Halligan MP，所以基本上
are leveraging the underlying Illidan
正在利用潜在的伊利丹
ase platform to basically build harridan
ase平台基本建立哈里丹
MP next to that we have an additional
议员旁边，我们有一个额外的
optional project which basically helped
可选项目，基本上有帮助
to integrate external services
整合外部服务
that's so that's part of the Hillen
那就是Hillen的一部分
project but the only thing that we need
项目，但我们唯一需要的是
to use all those components is basically
使用所有这些组件基本上是
CDI so you can take those service
CDI，因此您可以接受这些服务
integration and use it use them using
集成并使用它使用
any micro profile implementation so if
任何微型配置文件的实现，如果
we look at the capability of those three
我们来看这三个的能力
core components the reactive web server
响应式Web服务器的核心组件
simple so it provides simple functional
简单，因此提供简单的功能
routing model with reactive flow API
具有反应流API的路由模型
that's something that we will see later
那是我们稍后会看到的
on it's built on Letty it provides
基于它提供的Letty
tracing metrics and health check
跟踪指标和健康检查
capability again that's something that
能力再次是那件事
we will also leverage on the micro
我们还将利用微型
profile side something which is also
侧面的东西也是
important to keep in mind so we have two
重要的是要记住，所以我们有两个
level we have a lead on SC and then we
级别，我们在SC方面有领先优势，然后我们
have a lead on MP having said that there
有一个领先的国会议员说，那里
are some capabilities some API from L in
有一些来自L的API的功能
an MP micro profile that you can use on
可用于的MP微型配置文件
the AC side typically you can use Jersey
AC端通常可以使用Jersey
on the Heron and SC side if you want to
如果你想在苍鹭和南卡罗来纳州
do so JSON P so it's also an API that
这样做JSON P，所以它也是一个API
you can use on the AC side just don't
您可以在交流侧使用
build another one but typically you will
再建一个，但是通常你会
I likely not want to use CDI on the AC
我可能不想在AC上使用CDI
side if you want to use CDI you would
如果您想使用CDI，
have to go on the micro profile side so
必须在微型侧面
directive web server also provide a
指令Web服务器还提供了
capability to do static web serving so
能够进行静态Web服务的功能
it's not it's not a full-blown web
这不是一个成熟的网站
server but if your application if your
服务器，但如果您的应用程序
services need to do some basic web
服务需要做一些基本的网页
serving that's something that you can do
服务是你可以做的
directly within your Allegiant SC
直接在您的Allegiant SC中
application now if we look at the config
现在，如果我们查看配置
the configuration component that's a
配置组件是
component that you can use to basically
您可以用来基本
deal with configuration so it it support
处理配置，使其支持
multiple data source in terms of the
多个数据源
test words we're talking about
测试我们正在谈论的单词
properties file simple files and so on
属性文件，简单文件等
and so on it support different tough so
等它支持不同的困难
that you can use to process those data
您可以用来处理这些数据的
source so like JSON hawk on and so on
来源，例如JSON hawk等等
and so on and it's also support yourself
等等，这也可以养活自己
the ability to fetch your resources
获取资源的能力
sorry your configuration from different
对不起，您的配置来自其他
source such as for example each CD or
来源，例如每个CD或
gate or a plane endpoint those kind of
门或平面端点
things and you can also extend that so
事情，你也可以扩展它
you can for example I have JSON
你可以例如我有JSON
both through a get hand point and you
两者都通过掌握观点而你
can easily consume that and you can also
可以很容易地消耗掉它，你也可以
deal with configuration in specific
具体处理配置
formats so if you're not happy with the
格式，如果您不满意
format that are provided out of the box
开箱即用的格式
you have the ability to extend and hide
你有能力扩展和隐藏
your home parser for the ring with your
您的家用解析器与您的戒指
own code configuration format so exactly
自己的代码配置格式非常精确
the idea is that it's an attraction on
这个想法是它对
all the configuration once you fetch the
一旦您获取了所有配置
configuration you will basically have an
配置，您将基本上有一个
in-memory tree that you can access
您可以访问的内存树
access transparently from your
从您的透明访问
application you can also had Pooler so
您也可以使用Pooler的应用程序
the idea is that once you fetch the
想法是，一旦您获取了
notification sorry once you fetch the
收到通知后，抱歉
configuration maybe you want to know
配置也许你想知道
that that given configuration has been
给定的配置已经
updated so the configuration in itself
已更新，因此配置本身
is immutable so it will not change but
是不可变的，因此不会改变，但是
if the outside configuration has been
如果外部配置已经
changed that's something that you maybe
改变了那也许是你
want to know within your code so that's
想知道您的代码中，所以
something that is perfectly possible so
完全有可能的事情
you can attach some kind of listener to
您可以将某种侦听器附加到
be notified that that configuration
收到该配置的通知
properties has been updated for example
例如，属性已更新
and as but not least the security
作为但并非最不重要的安全
component that will basically allows you
基本上可以让您
to secure your application so out of the
保护您的应用程序安全
box it provide authentication
提供身份验证的框
authorization outbound security holy
授权出站安全圣
thing and so on and so on so right now
东西等等等等等等
we are providing different providers so
我们提供不同的提供商，所以
there's the GWT HTTP basic HTTP digest
有GWT HTTP基本HTTP摘要
google logging out on so there is a
谷歌登出，所以有一个
Google login providers there's no high
Google登录提供商不高
DC and so on and so on so I don't evolve
DC等等等，所以我不会发展
that well I don't remember remember all
好吧，我不记得了
of them so look at the docs so that's
他们中的，所以看看文档，这是
basically the three core components of
基本上是三个核心组成部分
eridan SE and you will use those
eridan SE，您将使用那些
components to build your application so
组件来构建您的应用程序
this is a snip set of a very basic
这是一个非常基本的片段集
adenine SC application so you see that
腺嘌呤SC应用程序，所以您会看到
to create a web server we are basically
创建一个Web服务器，我们基本上
using some of the concepts that we have
使用我们已有的一些概念
on the JavaScript side note typically so
在JavaScript旁注通常如此
web server create convention over
Web服务器创建约定
configuration so if we don't specify
配置，所以如果我们不指定
anything we will assume the default the
我们将采用默认值的任何内容
default value once we have a web server
有网络服务器后的默认值
credit we need to provide some routine
信用，我们需要提供一些常规
so this is a simple routing definition
所以这是一个简单的路由定义
routing is basically you tie together an
路由基本上就是你绑在一起
HTTP method with some path mapping so
HTTP方法带有一些路径映射，因此
for example in this case I'm just
例如在这种情况下，我只是
specifying that in this case I'm gonna
指定在这种情况下，我要
answer to any HTTP method so get put
任何HTTP方法的答案，请放
post delete and so on and so on on this
发布删除等，依此类推
path and this is called a handler so a
路径，这称为处理程序，因此
handler basically gets a request and a
处理程序基本上得到一个请求和一个
response and we can easily change
响应，我们可以轻松更改
together multiple under under so a
在一起下多个
handler would typically provide a
处理程序通常会提供
response so it will send a response to
回应，因此它将回应
the to the to the remote endpoint that's
到远程端点的
what we are doing here using the
我们在这里使用
response objects or responded sense will
回应对象或回应感
send a hello Helen on AC but we can also
在AC上向你问好海伦，但我们也可以
check them together so a handler can
一起检查它们，以便处理程序可以
also be can also filter for example so
也可以例如这样
the the idea is that we would have one
这个想法是，我们将有一个
handler first that will basically invoke
首先会基本调用的处理程序
the another handler that would be that
另一个处理程序是
would do something else and at the end
会做其他事情，最后
of the day the final handler will good
当天的最终处理程序会很好
hiders send the response to the
藏身者将回应发送给
connected remote endpoint or or it will
连接的远程端点，否则它将
throw an error that will be handled so
抛出将被处理的错误
we're defining our routing we are using
我们正在定义我们正在使用的路由
a build pattern so we build the object
构建模式，所以我们构建对象
and the only thing that we have to do to
而我们要做的唯一一件事
actually a bootstrap everything is
实际上是一个引导程序
invoke the staff method on the web
在网络上调用staff方法
server and there we go we have a small
服务器，我们走了，我们有一个小
web server that is running in ellen
在ellen中运行的Web服务器
honest so Helen and C is one thing then
老实说，海伦和C是一回事
we have a linen MP which is by now which
我们有一个亚麻MP，现在
is based on micro profiles so anybody
基于微观特征，因此任何人
knows what anybody doesn't know what
知道什么人不知道什么
micro profile is no so in a nutshell
简而言之，事实并非如此
it's basically a set of specification
这基本上是一组规范
which were started by reddit IBM to meet
由reddit IBM发起，以满足他们
Rob and Pyrrha
罗伯与皮拉
when Java EE was kind of in flux so they
当Java EE不断发展，所以他们
decided to work and try to leverage the
决定努力并尝试利用
divide that form to define additional
划分形式定义其他
API that are more targeted towards macro
更加针对宏的API
services since then Oracle has joined
从那时起，Oracle服务便加入了
that is initiatives and right now micro
这是倡议，现在是微
profile is at micro profile to the two
轮廓是两个的微观轮廓
so it basically a time-based
所以基本上是基于时间的
specification so every I think six
规格，所以我想每六个
months they are doing a release with
他们正在与几个月发布
whatever is available so that's what we
有什么可用的，这就是我们
are using for the more enterprise side
用于更多的企业方面
of Haledon I live in mp so this is
Haledon的居民我住在mp，所以这是
Helene an MP now let's zoom on the macro
议员海伦（Helene）现在让我们放大宏
profile side and see where we are today
侧面，看看我们今天在哪里
with Iranian MP so we first started by
与伊朗国会议员，所以我们首先开始
supporting a micro profile 1.0 so jax-rs
支持micro profile 1.0，所以jax-rs
CDI and JSONP right now we are
CDI和JSONP现在我们是
supporting a 1 micro profile 1 2 so that
支持1个微轮廓1 2
means that we support the configuration
表示我们支持配置
api of micro profile we are supporting
我们支持的微型配置文件的api
matrix API I'll check for turns and GWT
矩阵API，我将检查转弯和GWT
out technically we're also supporting
从技术上讲，我们也在支持
JSON be on the current Helena release
JSON在当前的Helena版本中
doesn't be is part of micro profile - so
不属于微观档案-因此
right now we're bidding between micro
现在我们在微
profile 1.2 and 2.2 and obviously we are
配置文件1.2和2.2，显然我们是
working on having full compliance of
努力完全遵守
micro profile 2.2 so as I mentioned MP
微型档案2.2，正如我提到的MP
is based on AC so if we look for example
基于交流，所以如果我们看例如
the micro profile configuration API is
微型配置文件配置API是
different that what we're what we have
与我们所拥有的不同
on the AC side having said that under
在交流方面说
the hood the micro profile config API in
引擎盖中的微配置文件配置API
Haledon MP is obviously using the
Haledon MP显然正在使用
harridan AC config api so this is what
哈里丹交流配置API，所以这就是
rest endpoint looks like in harridan MP
其余端点在harridan MP中看起来像
that's basically jax-rs there's really
基本上是jax-rs，
nothing new on that front
在这方面没有新内容
that's an API that we have all been
这是我们所有人都曾使用过的API
using for years so we have a we have a
使用多年，所以我们有一个
class with one method in this case so
在这种情况下使用一种方法的类
this is a resource method that were
这是一种资源方法
annotating with the HUD get annotation
用HUD注释获取注释
so this one will answer to the HTTP GET
所以这将回答HTTP GET
request under the Hat path hello path
帽子路径下的请求
and whenever we have a request it will
每当我们有要求时
just return hello Haledon MP so that's
只是向你问好Haledon MP，所以
basically the same example that we had
基本上和我们之前的例子相同
before but written using a lead on MP so
之前，但在MP上使用线索编写，因此
very quickly I mentioned that optional
我很快提到了可选
CDI extension project that is part of
属于CDI扩展项目
harridan but that's not something that
哈里丹，但那不是那个
you need to necessarily use so right now
您需要立即使用
we are providing three extension one to
我们提供了三个扩展名之一
connect to a database want to connect
连接到数据库要连接
Redis and want to connect to the Oracle
Redis并想连接到Oracle
cloud object
云对象
or under the hood we just need CDI so
或在后台我们只需要CDI，所以
that means that you can use them given
这意味着您可以使用给定的
that they're open source with any other
他们与其他任何人都是开源的
micro profile implementation this is out
微型配置文件的实现
the data source extension looks like you
数据源扩展看起来像你
first need to define to define your
首先需要定义以定义您的
configuration for example using the
配置，例如使用
micro profile configuration API so
微型配置文件配置API
that's property files that would be on
那将是属性文件
in this case on the class pass so you
在这种情况下，通过课程就可以了
define everything in your config file
在配置文件中定义所有内容
and then you are using CDI to inject
然后您使用CDI注入
that data source connection and from
该数据源连接以及
that point on you can use e use the
关于这一点，您可以使用e使用
other data source connection in your
您的其他数据源连接
anonymity micro profile code so let's
匿名微个人资料代码，让我们
have a look and see that in action it's
看一看，实际上是
demo that's a joke that only works in
演示只是开玩笑
Tokyo because it's demo is a famous shop
东京，因为它的演示是著名的商店
in Tokyo so it's demo time
在东京，现在是演示时间
so what we're gonna see today well we
所以我们今天会看到的很好
first look at how we can easily
首先看看我们如何轻松
bootstrap Haledon I see an MP
引导Haledon我看到了国会议员
application we'll have a look at some of
应用程序，我们将看一些
the config API we'll check some basic
配置API，我们将检查一些基本
routing maybe some JSON handling we'll
路由一些JSON处理，我们将
probably try docker and then we will
可能尝试docker，然后我们将
also have a look at kubernetes because
也看看kubernetes，因为
one of the things that we're doing with
我们正在做的一件事
a lid on is basically so we're giving
基本上是盖子，所以我们给
you a framework that you can easily use
您可以轻松使用的框架
to write web services that of this image
编写该图像的Web服务
and that at the end of the day you will
最终，您将
deploy those web services so we are
部署这些Web服务，以便我们
trying to bootstrap how you can easily
尝试引导您如何轻松
create how you can easily docker eyes
创建如何轻松地泊坞窗
your harridan code once it's dr. eyes
你的哈里丹代码，一旦博士。眼睛
obviously you can deploy it in docker in
显然，您可以将其部署在docker中
kubernetes sorry so let's have a look at
kubernetes对不起，让我们看一下
that in action that would be more clear
行动起来会更清楚
so the first thing that I'm gonna do so
所以我要做的第一件事
is there a way to to adjust the Beamer
有没有办法调整投影仪
because it's very no so the first thing
因为这不是第一件事
that I'm gonna do is bootstrap and
我要做的是引导程序，
Haledon application so for that we are
Haledon申请，因此我们
providing a maven archetype so maven
提供一个Maven原型
archetype generate you can use it to
原型生成您可以使用它来
bootstrap Eider and headed an AC
引导Eider并担任AC
application or an Haledon MP application
应用程序或Haledon MP应用程序
yeah the colors are very funky okay very
是的，颜色很时髦，很好
good
好
so if we look at Quick Start SC we have
因此，如果我们看一下Quick Start SC，
a bunch of file which have been created
一堆已创建的文件
for us and if you see there is a pun
对我们来说，如果您看到有一个双关语
file so it's basically just a maven
文件，所以它基本上只是一个专家
project so we can use our ID so let's
项目，这样我们就可以使用我们的ID，让我们
have a look at what we are here let's
看看我们在这里，让我们
see first so in the source so we see
首先在源中看到，所以我们看到
that we have a docker directory or Java
我们有一个docker目录或Java
directory and a community directory and
目录和社区目录，以及
a resource directory so let's have a
资源目录，所以我们有一个
look at the Java directory we have two
看一下Java目录，我们有两个
classes great services and main services
一流的服务和主要服务
so this is this is the application which
所以这是应用程序
has been generated so let's have a look
已经生成了，让我们来看一下
at what's there so in what in the main
主要是什么
is that is it readable at the end at the
在末尾是否可读
back yeah so we have one methods that
是的，所以我们有一种方法
stuff so so that's where basically
东西，所以基本上就是那里
everything will happen so if you look at
一切都会发生，所以如果你看
the starts over well what are we doing
从头开始，我们在做什么
in there so first we just configure the
在这里，所以我们首先配置
lock manager there is nothing fancy
锁管理器没有花哨
there and then we are basically creating
在那里，然后我们基本上在创建
a config object so by doing that again
一个配置对象，所以再做一次
convention over configuration given
约定优于配置
given that here I'm not specifying
鉴于这里我没有指定
anything out of the box I will have
开箱即用的任何东西
access to the
进入
a file that is on my class pass so that
我班上通过的文件，以便
mean that if I look at my class pass
就是说，如果我看我的课程准证
resources I should have an application
资源我应该有一个应用程序
of Java so that's basically where I will
Java的基础，这基本上就是我要去的地方
store my configuration so this is a ML
存储我的配置，所以这是一个机器学习
file it could have been a JSON file or
文件，它可能是JSON文件，或者
it had it could have been well Java
如果本来可以很好的Java
properties file and so on and so on
属性文件等等
that's something that is handled
那是要处理的东西
directly for you by the framework so you
直接由框架为您服务，因此您
don't have to deal with that so if we go
不必处理，所以如果我们去
back to the source I mean so config that
回到源头，我的意思是这样配置
create we have access to our
创建我们可以访问我们的
configuration so the next thing that we
配置，接下来我们
are doing we are creating a server
在做我们正在创建服务器
configuration object again for doing
再次配置对象
that we are just using the create method
我们只是在使用create方法
and here we are using sorry server
这里我们使用对不起的服务器
configuration here we just want to
在这里配置我们只想
access the configuration which is in our
访问我们的配置
configuration file so for that I can
配置文件，以便我可以
access that configuration using just
只需使用即可访问该配置
just a standard key dotted notation so
只是一个标准的点缀符号所以
the only configuration that I really
我真正的唯一配置
need here is the server configuration
这里需要的是服务器配置
which is basically if I look here that's
基本上，如果我看这里
the minimum I need to provide let's see
我需要提供的最低限度让我们看看
resource application and server is
资源应用程序和服务器是
basically just a port and binding
基本上只是一个端口和绑定
address that's all I need to provide ok
我需要提供的地址就可以了
so we have this web server configuration
所以我们有这个Web服务器配置
file so server config here so what we
文件，因此服务器配置在这里，所以我们
can do next we can actually create the
可以做的下一步，我们可以实际创建
web server so web server create we pass
网络服务器，以便网络服务器创建我们通过
this configuration file sorry
这个配置文件不好意思
and we also pass this create routing
我们也通过了这个创建路由
method with that get the config in in
的方法中获取配置
parameters so if we look at the
参数，所以如果我们看一下
configured of sorry if we get the create
如果得到创建，对不起
routing method that's basically where we
基本上是我们的路由方法
will create all our routines for that
将为此创建所有例程
given what server so the first thing
给什么服务器，所以第一件事
that we do we really we are creating a
我们确实在创造一个
matrix we're having matrix support so we
矩阵我们有矩阵支持，所以我们
want to have middlee support within our
希望在我们内部获得中间人支持
microservices then we are creating these
微服务，那么我们正在创建这些
a great service object which
一个很棒的服务对象
is really well we'll all come back to
真的很好，我们都会回到
that one later so let's let's move on to
稍后再说，让我们继续
this C main so we are creating this
这个C main，所以我们正在创建这个
grating object greeting service object
光栅对象问候服务对象
so we are here and then we just other
所以我们在这里，然后我们
whatever and we are providing two in
随便什么，我们提供两个
this case this is a consumer so once it
这种情况下，这是一个消费者，所以一旦
started we have with an accept method so
开始我们有一个accept方法
basically that's a consumer that will
基本上，这是一个会
just do something when the web server is
只需在Web服务器处于
actually started so in this case the
实际上开始，所以在这种情况下
only thing that we are doing
我们正在做的唯一的事情
we're just displaying the endpoint of
我们只是显示
our server and that's it
我们的服务器就是这样
and we also have this exceptionally buzz
而且我们也有这个特别的嗡嗡声
because basically what we have here is a
因为基本上我们在这里是一个
completion stage so either the server
完成阶段，因此服务器
can start so we're good or it fail in
可以开始，所以我们很好，否则失败了
that case we have the exceptional
那样的话，我们有例外
limited that we can pass it a function
限制我们可以将其传递给函数
to do something in case something goes
做某事以防万一
wrong and in that case the only thing
错误的，在那种情况下唯一的事情
that we can do is basically just display
我们可以做的基本上只是显示
the stack trace
堆栈跟踪
so our web server is started so
所以我们的网络服务器启动了
everything is really happening up happen
一切都真的发生了
happening here so if we go back to the
发生在这里，所以如果我们回到
create routine method so we have the
创建常规方法，以便我们
metrics we have the grid services we're
指标，我们拥有网格服务
also having a head health support out of
也有来自头部的健康支持
the box the has capability nearly done
具有几乎完成功能的盒子
our is is providing a few health checks
我们正在提供一些健康检查
that you can use you can also add your
您可以使用的还可以添加您的
own so typically you would had specific
拥有，所以通常你会有特定的
customers check for your own application
客户检查自己的应用程序
but we are providing a few
但是我们提供了一些
out-of-the-box like the hip size the
开箱即用的髋部尺寸
disk size and I can't remember which one
磁盘大小，我不记得是哪一个
anyway that's what I'm doing here I'll
无论如何，这就是我在这里要做的
check health check basically I'm just
检查健康检查基本上我只是
hiding the default health check that
隐藏默认的健康检查
Helen is providing me I built that
海伦为我提供了我建立的
object and finally what I'm doing here
对象，最后我在这里做什么
I'm actually constructing all the
我实际上正在构建所有
routing for my method so I'm heading
为我的方法路由，所以我要去
JSON support that's something that is in
JSON支持
this case I'm JSON support is needed
这种情况下我需要JSON支持
header for else or or matrix I never
我从来没有的其他或矩阵的标题
remember which one is outputting JSON
记住哪一个正在输出JSON
anyway so we're adding JSON support we
无论如何，所以我们要添加JSON支持，
are also having our health
也很健康
checked object so that we can watch
检查对象，以便我们可以观看
basically we are just registering all
基本上我们只是在注册所有
our L stack which have been defined in
我们的L堆栈已经在
this case this is just the default one
在这种情况下，这只是默认情况
we're having the metrics and finally
我们有了指标，最后
we're also defining that our end points
我们还定义了我们的终点
so whenever we reach the slash grid path
所以只要我们到达斜线网格路径
we're gonna use these great services
我们将使用这些出色的服务
endpoints which is defined here so if we
端点在这里定义，所以如果我们
look at that guy there's nothing really
看着那个家伙，真的没有
fancy here it implements this services
喜欢在这里实现这项服务
interface and basically we need to
界面，基本上我们需要
override this update method so that's
覆盖此更新方法，因此
basically where we her we are updating
基本上我们在更新她
the routing rules so what we are doing
路由规则，所以我们在做什么
here we are defining a new rules so
在这里，我们定义了一个新规则，因此
whenever there is a get request on the
每当有一个获取请求
on on route so great slash basically we
在路线上，这样的斜线基本上我们
are using the default message angler
使用默认的消息钓鱼者
whenever there is a request that is
每当有一个请求
passing a pass param we're using this
通过传递参数，我们正在使用这个
message angler and whenever there is a
消息钓鱼者，只要有
request for the put method we are using
请求我们使用的put方法
this update greeting Handler and we can
这个更新问候处理程序，我们可以
have a look at those so basically this
基本上看看这些
one will just return hello well so it
一个人会很好地返回你好，所以它
doesn't change any further handler it
不会更改任何其他处理程序
just sent a response source and response
刚刚发送了响应源和响应
and it just had a world the this one
它只是有一个世界，这个世界
basically the same but in this case it
基本相同，但在这种情况下
uses the parameter which has which was
使用具有
part of the initial request so a hello
初始请求的一部分，所以您好
and the given parameters and your one
以及给定的参数和您的
are just used to update the gratings
只是用来更新光栅
that we have so let's see that in action
我们拥有的，让我们来看一下
so this is basically a simple Halden MSC
所以这基本上是一个简单的Halden MSC
application so
这样申请
so that's normal so maybe you didn't
所以那很正常所以也许你没有
have the time but when we build the the
有时间，但是当我们建立
services of you see we're testing the
你们的服务看到我们正在测试
services and the test pass web snows our
服务和测试通过网络下雪了我们
web server is down I think that's
网络服务器故障我认为
because of my firewall anyway I will use
因为我的防火墙，我将继续使用
it directly and we'll see that so if we
它直接，我们会看到的，如果我们
go here we have a jar QuickStart I see
去这里，我们有一个罐子快速入门，我看到了
jar so that's basically our just the
罐子，所以基本上这只是我们的
application that we have
我们拥有的应用程序
so we don't space we don't pass anything
所以我们不空间我们什么都不传递
we have the hello world we pass it a
我们有一个你好世界，我们通过了
param hello folks and so on and so on so
向人们打招呼，等等等等
you get the ID so what I can do next so
您获得了ID，接下来我该怎么做
I have my my my application so my jar
我有我的我的应用程序，所以我的罐子
I can easily docker eyes that
我可以轻松地泊坞窗
application using if I can type so out
应用程序是否可以键入
of the box were providing a docker file
包装盒中提供了一个docker文件
so Haledon late a lead on AC latest has
所以Haledon最近在AC方面领先了
been built so now we can docker run that
已经建立，所以现在我们可以泊坞窗运行
one
一
- so there's nothing running in my
-所以我的身上什么也没有
daugher
道尔
so docker run and then the name of the
所以docker run然后是
image which is
图像是
it started and obviously you see that it
它开始了，显然你看到了
works and now if I do go docker PS you
工作，现在，如果我去docker PS you
see that it fun within docker so you see
看到它在docker中很有趣，所以您看到了
that we have the application running in
我们有应用程序在其中运行
docker and now if I kill it obviously it
码头工人，现在，如果我将其杀死，显然
will not work so that's you see that's
将无法工作，所以那是你看到的是
an easy way to basically from pure Helen
简单地从纯Helen转变为简单方法
and C code movie to docker we can also
和C代码电影到docker我们也可以
move it move that that to communities so
将其移至社区
let's see and get so I have a
让我们看看并得到，所以我有一个
communities cluster running here yep I
我在这里运行的社区集群
can see get so
可以看到变得如此
let's sorry get both body so you see
让我们感到抱歉，让你两身都这样
that star se is running so now to access
那颗星星在运行，所以现在可以访问
it I need to get
我需要得到
so this is the IP and so now it's run
这是IP，因此现在可以运行
within my community's cluster so the
在我的社区集群中
same code is running within my community
我的社区中正在运行相同的代码
cluster so localhost hello world
集群所以本地主机你好世界
so basically you saw that very quickly
所以基本上你很快就看到了
we were able to put strap on a lead on
我们能够在表带上戴上皮带
AC application move it to docker and
AC应用程序将其移至docker
then deploy it to communities so kiss
然后将其部署到社区，以便接吻
and now I need to make sure I'd delete
现在我需要确定要删除
it for the rest of my okay okay okay so
剩下的我就好吧好吧好吧所以
that's in a nutshell I know five minutes
简而言之，我知道五分钟
a five minute overview of a lead on Etsy
五分钟的Etsy潜在客户概述
so we've quickly discussed several
所以我们很快讨论了几个
configuration startup routing JSON I
配置启动路由JSON I
will discuss Jason in this application
将在此应用程序中讨论Jason
so the next thing that I would like to
所以接下来我想
show you is basically how we integrate
告诉你基本上是我们如何整合
growl with Haledon so pretty sure that
与Haledon咆哮，非常确定
most of you knows growl so growl is a
你们大多数人都知道咆哮，所以咆哮是
universal hyperfont Polly got the other
通用超字体Polly得到了另一个
machine it provides lots of capacity
机器，它提供了很大的容量
like the ability for example to do no
喜欢例如不做的能力
overriding interoperability between
两者之间的互操作性
different language but one of the things
语言不同，但其中之一
that we are very keen to use on the hill
我们非常想在山上使用
a downside is the IOT so the high ahead
物联网的缺点是，未来的发展
of time ahead of time compilation that
提前编译的时间
is provided by Crowell so the idea is
由Crowell提供，所以这个想法是
that you will basically start with a
基本上，您将从
some Java code growl we'll take the Java
一些Java代码咆哮我们将采用Java
code and it will do the head of time
代码，它将花很多时间
compilation of that code so that at the
该代码的编译，以便在
end of the day what we get is a native
一天结束时，我们得到的是本地人
Linux exotic executable that will embed
将嵌入的Linux外来可执行文件
a specific virtual machine because
特定的虚拟机，因为
remember that we are talking from Java
记住我们是在用Java聊天
code so that means that we need to have
代码，这意味着我们需要
memory management we need to have some
内存管理，我们需要一些
thread management and so on and so on
线程管理等
typically the capability that is that
通常的能力是
that is provided by the Java Virtual
由Java Virtual提供
Machine
机
but obviously given that where we have
但显然，鉴于我们拥有
at the end of the day or not even Linux
在一天结束时甚至没有Linux
executable that's not something that we
可执行文件不是我们要做的
can use from the outside world
可以从外面使用
so basically rel will embed the
所以基本上rel将嵌入
substrate VM directly within our
直接在我们内部的基板VM
executable so let's have a look at that
可执行文件，所以让我们看一下
so what I have here is a basic project
所以我这里是一个基础项目
so let me first kill that guy so it's
我先杀了那个家伙
simple well it's a relatively simple
好吧，这是一个相对简单的
application so let's try to quickly
应用程序，所以让我们尝试快速
understand what the application is doing
了解应用程序在做什么
so everything start from here so this
所以一切都从这里开始
you can safely ignore that's something
你可以放心地忽略那件事
that we it's just a workaround for the
我们只是针对
yam el paso that we're using because
我们使用的yam el paso是因为
there's a burglar well there is a bug in
有个防盗井，里面有个虫子
that path that of will be a result very
那条路将是非常结果
soon so that's not something which is
很快，那不是什么
important so we're creating a config
重要，因此我们正在创建一个配置
object right then we're creating a
对象，然后我们创建一个
server configuration in that server
该服务器中的服务器配置
configuration we are defining a
我们定义的配置
traitor's a tracer so we want to use
叛徒是示踪剂，所以我们想使用
basically zip tins open tracing we want
基本上我们想要的拉链罐打开跟踪
to add tracing directly within our
在我们的内部直接添加跟踪
application then we are creating a web
应用程序，然后我们创建一个网站
server like we saw right before so we
像我们之前看到的服务器，所以我们
create a web server using these specific
使用这些特定的工具来创建Web服务器
routing so we'll check that so then we
路由，因此我们将对其进行检查，然后我们
start a web server if everything goes
如果一切正常，请启动Web服务器
well we're happy if everything doesn't
好吧，如果一切都没有，我们很高兴
go so well we're not so happy so let's
进行得如此顺利，我们不是很高兴，所以让我们
have a look at this routing method so
看一下这个路由方法
that's basically where we define all the
基本上就是我们定义所有
routing for our services so the first
为我们的服务进行路由，因此第一个
thing that we we say here we define here
我们在这里说的东西在这里定义
we basically just get some message from
我们基本上只是从
the configuration object so basically in
所以配置对象基本上在
this case that would be from the UML
这种情况将来自UML
file in the class pass but it could have
文件通过类传递，但它可能有
been another data source it doesn't
是另一个数据源
really matter then we are defining a
真的很重要，然后我们定义一个
network support so we want to have
网络支持，所以我们想拥有
tracing within the application but we
在应用程序中进行跟踪，但是我们
also want to have metrics out of the box
也想开箱即用
provided by the application we're
由我们提供的应用程序提供
specifying a specific custom Condor
指定特定的自定义神鹰
right
对
and not only that were also having el
不仅如此，
sexual support directly in our in our
性支持直接在我们体内
application so in this case let's see we
应用程序，所以在这种情况下，让我们看看
are using one of the provided air sacs
正在使用提供的气囊之一
OHIP memory check and we are so heading
OHIP内存检查，我们正朝着这个方向前进
here a custom I'll check so this one
这是我要检查的习惯，所以这个
will just basically provide some timing
基本上会提供一些时间
information so basically since when
信息基本上从什么时候开始
well not just not even since when so
不仅如此
basically some some timing nothing more
基本上是一些时机
than that so we have tracing we are we
而不是那样，所以我们一直在追踪我们
have matrix we have health check we're
有矩阵，我们有健康检查
also adding security so we won't figure
还增加了安全性，所以我们不会
some of our rest endpoint so we are
我们其余的一些终点，所以我们
basically using the three core component
基本上使用了三个核心部分
of harridan AC so then we just need to
的哈里丹AC，所以我们只需要
basically register all our routing rules
基本上注册我们所有的路由规则
so with OG star the matrix we register
因此，对于OG星，我们注册的矩阵
the web security Weaver just saw the
网络安全性Weaver刚看到
health and then we didn't need to define
健康，然后我们不需要定义
the endpoint themselves so the first one
端点本身，所以第一个
slash basically we have a standard
斜线基本上我们有一个标准
handlers slash admin will be a bit
处理程序斜线管理员将有点
different so this one is secure we can
不同，所以这是安全的，我们可以
check how it's secure if we are if we go
如果我们去的话，检查它的安全性
in the configuration file so we see that
在配置文件中，所以我们看到
we are in the configuration file to also
我们在配置文件中也
define the security we can define the
定义安全性我们可以定义
security either programmatically or
以编程方式或
through configuration or we can mix and
通过配置，或者我们可以混合使用
match so basically we are defining on
匹配，所以基本上我们在定义
HTTP basic authentication your
HTTP基本认证
configuration file this is just for demo
配置文件，仅用于演示
obviously we can do areas and store them
显然我们可以做区域并存储它们
in a secure store so we have to user one
在一个安全的商店中，所以我们必须使用一个
is a as the role admin and the other one
是作为角色管理员，另一个
has the role a user and then we just
扮演用户角色，然后我们就
need to specify which path we want to
需要指定我们想要的路径
secure so admin can only be accessed by
安全，因此管理员只能由
admin users I mean sorry user within the
管理员用户我的意思是对不起用户
admin role and slash JSON can also can
管理员角色和斜杠JSON也可以
only be accessed by user that has either
仅由具有以下任一功能的用户访问
a user role or a head Monroe
用户角色或首席门罗
so where are we so okay so we are here
所以我们在哪里还好，所以我们在这里
so we have this admin which is secure
所以我们有这个管理员是安全的
then we are defining this JSON endpoint
然后我们定义这个JSON端点
which is also secure and for that we are
这也是安全的，因此我们
hiding in JSON support
隐藏在JSON支持中
J'son be here so slashes NB we will also
詹森（J'son）在这里
use not JSON P but Jason B so basically
基本上不使用JSON P，而是使用Jason B
the ability to directly output Java
直接输出Java的能力
object that will be marshal to JSON
将封送至JSON的对象
document by the endpoint so if we go
通过端点记录，所以如果我们去
back
背部
you
您
so this is an application that has Jason
所以这是一个具有Jason的应用程序
B support JSONP support security tracing
B支持JSONP支持安全性跟踪
matrix L check so let's try to run this
矩阵L检查，让我们尝试运行
application in cockade
在帽徽中的应用
so the application weight hedeman
因此应用重量Hedeman
kilobyte but that's just the jar of the
千字节，但这仅仅是
application I need to add to that all
我需要添加的所有应用程序
the libraries that are used and
使用的库和
obviously the runtime the Java Runtime
显然，运行时是Java Runtime
to run that we can run the application
运行，我们可以运行应用程序
and I have design point that I can use
我有可以使用的设计要点
to access the application so ello from
访问该应用程序，所以从
Samuel config so this is configure this
塞缪尔配置，所以这是配置
is coming from the configuration file if
来自配置文件，如果
I try to access admin obviously that
我显然尝试访问管理员
shouldn't work because that endpoint is
应该不起作用，因为该端点是
secured and if we look here there's
安全的，如果我们看这里
indeed an unauthorized access so that's
确实是未经授权的访问，因此
basically the Java side of the story
基本上是故事的Java方面
so nothing really new here what I'm
所以这里没有什么新鲜的东西
gonna do now I'm gonna use grill to
现在要做，我要用烤架
basically turn that Java code into a
基本上将Java代码变成了
native executor
本地执行者
executable and that's something that
可执行文件，那是
takes like two two minutes so let's see
大概需要两两分钟，让我们来看看
that's exactly the native image so what
那就是原始图像，所以
is happening here so basically first the
发生在这里，所以基本上首先
application is built using the regular
应用程序是使用常规构建的
Java tool chain and then growl growl
Java工具链，然后咆哮
will kick in to turn that into a native
将会把它变成一个本地人
executable that's something that takes a
可执行文件需要
bit of time so if you have any question
一点时间，所以如果您有任何问题
that would be a good time to ask your
那是问你的好时机
question we have like two minutes in
问题我们有两分钟
front of us no questions if you don't
如果没有的话，我们面前没有问题
have any questions I have good jokes
有什么问题我有很好的笑话
that are not funny when we bootstrap so
当我们引导时这并不有趣
whenever whenever I'm using the maven
每当我在使用Maven
archetype to bootstrap an application we
引导应用程序的原型
are providing the docker file and the
正在提供docker文件和
communities file for adenosine and a
社区申请腺苷和
little empty so this is a quite
有点空，这是一个相当
expensive operation but that's something
昂贵的操作，但这就是事实
that you only do at Build time and I
你只在构建时做，而我
don't know if you can hear but my fan or
不知道你能听见吗，但我的粉丝或
a kind of game going crazy but this
一种疯狂的游戏，但这
provides benefits you will see that in
提供的好处，您将看到
less than a minute
不到一分钟
three
三
which one will answer first it depends
哪个首先回答取决于
but just wait a minute you will see
但是等一下你会看到
because so clearly whenever you are
因为无论何时你都很清楚
deploying you don't want to use growl
部署您不想使用咆哮
that's not that's that's only something
那不是那只是一件事
that you will use when your application
在您的应用程序中将使用的
is basically ready to be deployed and
基本上可以部署了
we're getting there yes that's a good
我们到那里是的，这很好
point so there are a few limitations for
点，因此有一些限制
example today growl is limited to Java 8
今天的例子咆哮仅限于Java 8
so but they are working on an adding
因此，但他们正在努力增加
support for Java 11 and there are other
支持Java 11，还有其他功能
limitation like if you are using
限制，例如如果您使用
reflection you need to configure you do
反射你需要配置你做
you need to do some specific
你需要做一些具体的
configuration if you are doing every
配置，如果您正在做的每一件事
byte manipulation for example growl is
字节操作，例如咆哮是
probably not a good fit so there are a
可能不是一个很好的选择，所以有一个
few exception and few use case word it
很少有例外，用例很少
doesn't make sense or simply growl won't
没有道理或只是咆哮不会
work but for those type of application
工作，但对于那些类型的应用程序
that works so you see 2 minutes 21
有效，所以您看到2分钟21
seconds so let's have a look at what has
秒，让我们看一下
been generated so if we look here so you
已经生成，所以如果我们在这里看，那么你
see that we have these green headed an
看到我们有这些绿色的头
example native image 26 megabyte so this
例如本机映像26 MB，因此
is basically our application with
基本上是我们的应用程序
everything built-in because it's in this
所有内置的，因为它在
case this is a Mac native executable so
这是Mac原生可执行文件，因此
I can run it my firewall complain that's
我可以运行它，我的防火墙抱怨那是
fine so you see the application started
很好，所以您看到应用程序已启动
in in this case 11 millisecond so that's
在这种情况下，是11毫秒
the exact same application so it has
完全相同的应用程序
security it has tracing it has health
它具有跟踪功能，具有健康状态
check and so on and so on so I can show
检查等等等等，以便我可以显示
you that so I will just kill the
你那我就杀了
application and I will start for example
应用程序，我将开始举例
the pin
别针
so 1994 1-1 now let's rerun the
所以1994 1-1现在让我们重新运行
application yes
申请是
I'm wallowing that so now we've look for
我很想知道，所以现在我们要寻找
example at zip King so 9 4 1 yes there's
例如在zip King，所以9 4 1是的
no trace okay so now if I go here so if
没有痕迹好吧，所以现在如果我去这里，如果
I access the application hello from
我从访问应用程序你好
samyama if I go back go back to zip kins
samyama，如果我回去，回到邮编
fine trace hi one phrase again this is
良好的轨迹，嗨，又一个短语，这是
Java code basically that has been turned
Java代码基本上已经转向
into native code bye bye growl I can try
进入本机代码再见咆哮我可以尝试
to access the admin it will not work
访问管理员将无法正常工作
again if I go back here if I find traces
如果我找到痕迹又回到这里
and you see that indeed I was not
你看到我确实不是
allowed to access that resources not
允许不访问该资源
only that I also have access to health
只是我也有健康
check I think it's house no it's not
检查，我认为这是房子，不是
health you see that that's an arrow from
健康，你看到那是从
my keyboard because this is not a space
我的键盘，因为这不是空格
this is a space so this is basically the
这是一个空间，所以这基本上是
second formation that is provided by the
由
application and here yes we have our
应用程序，是的，我们有
custom health check provider that is
自定义健康检查提供者
provided providing just a hub state and
提供仅提供中心状态
some timing information and this is the
一些时间信息，这是
hip memory I'll stack provider that is
髋关节记忆，我将堆栈提供者
one of the standard built-in provider
标准内置提供程序之一
that we're also using what else so we we
我们也在使用其他东西，所以我们
have security we have health check
有安全我们有健康检查
we have tracing matrix a little bit
我们有一点追踪矩阵
matrix
矩阵
so this is the matrix not that are
所以这不是矩阵
provided out of the box so again keep in
提供开箱即用，因此再次保留
mind this is we're starting from Java
介意这是我们从Java开始
code so from a Haledon SC application
Haledon SC应用程序编写的代码
with JSON be JSON PC port security else
带有JSON是JSON PC端口安全性
check matrix and probably something else
检查矩阵，可能还有其他东西
the web server so basically most of the
网络服务器，基本上，大部分
capability that we have using RAL we
我们拥有使用RAL的能力
turn that in sorry not the right place
把它变成对不起，不是正确的地方
we turn that into a 26 megabyte
我们将其变成26兆字节
executable that we can obviously run
我们显然可以运行的可执行文件
within docker so if I docker eyes that
在泊坞窗内，如果我泊坞窗
let's see if I well to docker eyes it I
让我们看看我是否对码头工人的眼睛好吗
need to basically because what I have
需要基本上是因为我有
here is basically and well what we're
基本上，这就是我们
also providing is basically the ability
基本上也提供了能力
to dr. I to dr. eyes your your code but
去博士我给博士。看你的代码，但
for that we're using docker because
为此，我们使用docker是因为
obviously we need to produce a Linux
显然，我们需要生产一个Linux
executable that will run within docker
将在docker中运行的可执行文件
so we are doing that within docker
所以我们在docker里面做
container it's a bit tricky because we
容器有点棘手，因为我们
are using docker to and we are using
正在使用docker to，我们正在使用
within the docker the native image
在docker中，本机映像
capability of graal to produce native
格拉夫生产本地人的能力
image that will be run somewhere else so
该图像将在其他地方运行
that is growl in action so you see that
这是咆哮的，所以你看到
basically by combining Haledon and growl
基本上是通过结合Haledon和咆哮
you can achieve a very quick startup
您可以快速启动
time to answer back your question
是时候回答你的问题了
because if we look at this at at time of
因为如果我们在
this guy 18 milliseconds which is quite
这个家伙18毫秒
fast given that we are tracing support
快速，因为我们正在追踪支持
we have health check and so on and so on
我们有健康检查等等
in a 26 megabyte executable
在26兆字节的可执行文件中
when it's already started that's a good
当它已经开始，那是一个很好的
point so the thing that we have to
指出我们必须要做的事情
compare when whenever we're is in Java
比较何时使用Java
for example
例如
odd spot versus growl the stuff that
奇怪的地方与咆哮的东西
time on the Java side will I like he be
在Java方面的时间我会喜欢他吗
a slower but the thing that we have on
较慢但我们拥有的东西
the Java side with a JIT for example is
例如，带有JIT的Java端是
the optimization that will kick in after
之后将进行的优化
some sometimes we are working on some
有时候我们在做一些
benchmark so I can I can add this today
基准，所以我今天可以添加
I can not really give you any numbers
我真的不能给你任何数字
but in terms of footprints start-up time
但就足迹启动时间而言
memory consumption rally's very good now
内存消耗反弹现在非常好
over time if you have an application
随着时间的推移，如果您有一个应用程序
services that runs for days weeks months
运行数天至数月的服务
it may be a better idea to focus on the
专注于
pure performance aspect by using for
通过使用纯性能方面
example all the capability that we have
举例说明我们拥有的所有能力
in the standard java virtual machine
在标准的Java虚拟机中
because at the end of the day if you are
因为归根结底，如果你是
just starting the application once well
只需启动一次应用程序
so let's see
让我们来看看
that's also something to startup time
这也是启动时间
and so on and the footprint that I will
等等，我会足迹
discuss tomorrow in my service session
明天在我的服务会议上讨论
and I will discuss realm from a
我将讨论一个
different angle so I gave you a very
不同的角度，所以我给了你一个非常
quick overview of Haledon SC adenine MP
Haledon SC腺嘌呤MP的快速概述
is basically the pure standard micro
基本上是纯标准微
Rafael PI that one of the benefit with
拉斐尔·PI的好处之一
al-anon you have choice either you are
Al-anon您可以选择是
using AC s he give us the ability to
使用AC，他使我们能够
innovate because we are defining the API
创新，因为我们正在定义API
and the capability by ourself
和我们自己的能力
Allanon MP is safer and safer in the
Allanon MP在
sense that you are just using a standard
感觉到您只是在使用标准
so you can switch from a different
因此您可以从其他位置切换
microphone implementation go back and
麦克风实现可以追溯到
forth and so on and you most of the
等等，您大部分
developers know most of the micro
开发人员知道大多数微
profile API so it's easier to start with
个人资料API，因此更容易开始
those ones so where are we today so we
那些，所以我们今天在哪里，所以我们
launched ten point four in October we
在十月份我们推出了十点四
did a bunch of things and today we are
做了一堆事情，今天我们是
basically at 1.0.1 which was released
基本上在1.0.1发布
last week so in the last few months
上周，所以在过去的几个月中
there was a strong focus on making sure
人们非常注重确保
that we we are a 1.0 one of the things
我们是1.0的一件事
that we did in 1.0 we try to stabilize
我们在1.0中所做的尝试试图稳定
most of the API so except for a very few
大部分的API都是如此，除了少数
kind of case API the API that we have
一种案例API我们拥有的API
today are you well you can be assured
今天你很好，你可以放心
that they will be there for a long time
他们会在那里很长一段时间
they will not we won't break them
他们不会，我们不会破坏他们
so in 1.0 we have added support for
因此在1.0中，我们增加了对
Jason B yes on so there doesn't be
杰森B是的所以没有
reference implementation but also a
参考实现
Jackson so again you can choose which
杰克逊，所以你可以再次选择
JSON implementation you use and last
持续使用的JSON实现
week we've released the 1.0.1 few fixes
一周我们已经发布了1.0.1的一些修复程序
and also some specific stuff done for
还有一些特定的东西
making sure that browser works within le
确保浏览器可以在
donne I see something that I should
唐恩，我看到一些我应该
mention is that growl nearly done only
值得一提的是，咆哮几乎只能完成
works in a LaDonna see we are not sure
在LaDonna上工作，我们不确定
it makes sense to have Roth support for
罗斯支持
a lead on MP at this stage in terms of
在此阶段，MP方面的领先优势
roadmap so when the zero is done we are
路线图，所以当零完成时
supporting micro profile 1.2 so the next
支持micro profile 1.2，因此下一个
big thing is to work on making sure that
重要的是要努力确保
were we we are supporting all the micro
我们是否支持所有微型
profile to the
个人资料
to API we are also working on
到API，我们也在努力
persistence so having support for GP and
坚持不懈，因此对GP和
GTA on the macro profile side but also
GTA不仅在宏配置文件方面，而且在
on the SE side maybe exam sense and
在SE方面也许考试意义和
later on we are of a bunch of thing that
后来我们有很多事情
we would like to do like HTTP to support
我们想像HTTP一样支持
WebSockets support where so we will we
WebSockets支持我们在哪里
also want to have a website that you can
也想有一个可以
easily that you can use to is the
您可以轻松使用的是
bootstrap application stead of using the
引导应用程序而不是使用
maven archetype something that is more
Maven原型更重要
user friendly and so on and so on so we
用户友好等等等等，所以我们
have a lot of things that we want to do
有很多我们想做的事情
so in terms of prop up headed on a set
所以就支撑着一个场景而言
of Java libraries for developing micro
用于开发微型程序的Java库
services everything is open source so
服务一切都是开源的，所以
you can give it a try there's really no
您可以尝试一下，真的没有
cost associated with that those are the
与之相关的成本是
resources if you just need to remember
资源，如果您只需要记住
one link harridan dot io you have access
一个链接harridan dot io您可以访问
to all the resources including the
所有资源，包括
github repo and so on and we have a very
github repo等，我们有一个非常
good and well-designed documentation so
好的和精心设计的文档，因此
we have a CD to get started guide that
我们有一张CD入门指南，
will basically guide you step-by-step on
基本上会指导您逐步进行
how to write out to bootstrap an Illidan
如何写出引导伊利丹
LC or MP application how to do karai's
LC或MP应用程序如何执行karai的
it how to deploy to docker and now to go
它如何部署到docker，现在去
further so give it a try it doesn't cost
进一步尝试一下，不花钱
anything that's really something that we
任何真的是我们所需要的东西
would like you to do and if you like it
想要你做，如果你喜欢
give us a star it doesn't cost anything
给我们一颗星星，它不需要任何费用
but that's something that we really
但这是我们真正的事情
appreciate and with that almost in time
欣赏，几乎及时
I'd like to thank you for your time
我要感谢你的时间
I'm not sure if we have time for
我不确定我们是否有时间
questions do we you don't know either so
问题，我们也不知道吗
anyway I will be here so I still have a
无论如何，我会在这里，所以我仍然有一个
session tomorrow I think it's a keynote
明天的会议上，我认为这是一个主题演讲
session on Cerberus
关于Cerberus的会议
so just grab me or ask question now's I
所以就抓住我或问问题吧
mean if nobody kicks us out of the room
意思是如果没人把我们踢出房间
I can take questions
我可以提问
no no right now we re working on having
不，不，现在我们正在努力
performance numbers for just daily
每天的性能数字
downside so Haledon se le done MP Aaron
不利的一面让哈利登·塞勒完成了MP Aaron
and I see with growl and so on and so on
我看到咆哮等等
I mean we have a long list a long to-do
我的意思是我们还有很长的路要走
list so we're just focusing focusing on
清单，所以我们只专注于
ourself at this stage that's already a
我们自己在这个阶段已经是
lot of things to do yes just one I can
有很多事情要做，我可以
yeah no so in a nutshell yes but we
是的，简而言之，是的，但是我们
don't necessarily need all the
不一定需要所有
capability that we have annealing in
我们具有退火能力
Haledon se you will see tomorrow so le
哈利登SE，你明天会看到
done is a fast platform a service
完成是一个快速的平台服务
platform you will see tomorrow that a
平台，您明天将看到
function as well as function is
功能以及功能是
something very basic it's basically a
很基本的东西
method that get some input and produce
得到一些输入并产生的方法
some output nothing else in this case we
在这种情况下，我们没有其他输出
have quite a few capabilities that are
有很多功能
that we don't need like security all the
我们不需要像安全一样
way all the pass mapping and so on so
所有通过映射的方式等等
we're not using that and also function
我们不使用它，而且功能
most of the time you're invoking
大多数时候您在调用
function using HTTP but function can
使用HTTP功能，但功能可以
also be used invoked using a different
也可以使用不同的方式来调用
protocol like we have a scheduler or
像我们有一个调度程序或
maybe a queue for example so a function
也许队列，例如一个功能
a function in itself is not tied to http
一个功能本身并不绑定到http
here it's really HTTP hand points but
这实际上是HTTP的要点，但是
we're also for example using RAL on the
例如，我们还在
function side of the house any more
房子的功能面了
questions
问题
nope well then thanks to look for your
好吧，然后感谢您的寻找
time
时间
[Applause]
[掌声]